pandaexpress.com 2012-06-28

# Panda Express | Chinese Food, Wok-Cooked and Served Fast

The following statement discloses the privacy practices of Panda Restaurant Group, Inc., including Panda Express, Panda Inn and Hibachi San, effective September 22, 2005.

##  Information collection and use

Panda Restaurant Group, Inc., is the sole owner of the information collected on pandaexpress.com, mypandacard.com, pandainn.com, hibachisan.com and pandarg.com. We will not share, rent or sell the information to anyone in any way not described in this statement. We only gather personal information when voluntarilay submitted as discussed within this statement. 

##  online application

In the "Join Our Team" section of our web sites we have an employment application. The completion of this form is voluntary, and all information collected is routed to Human Resources in the form of an e-mail. 

##  surveys, contests and special offers

We may at time administer surveys, hold contests, or supply special offers to our database of users who have elected to let us contact them by e-mail. Participation in any of these on-line programs is voluntary, and our guests will always have the option to not supply information and/or opt out of programs. Information collected may include contact, demographic and opinion. Information may be used by third parties working on our behalf to contact a guest if they have won a contest, send special offers, or help us to determine the likes and preferences of consumers to better enhance our food, restaurants, overall customer experience, websites, and marketing. We will never make any of the information collected available to third parties other than solely on our behalf. 

##  panda card program

When and where available registration of the Panda Card is voluntary. Users of a Panda Card may register their cards on the mypandacard.com website. If you choose to register your card, we will collect personal information such as card number, birth date and e-mail address. We use this information as part of our Panda Card protection program and, if you choose, to provide you with targeted offers from the Panda Express restaurants. You may change your preference to receive offers at any time by visiting mypandacard.com and updating your account information. We may also collect information regarding your purchase behavior while using your Panda Card, used solely for the purpose of improving our Panda Express offerings, customer experience, marketing and advertising. 

##  Cookies

When you view our website we may store information on your computer called a "Cookie." A Cookie helps us to tailor our website to match your preferences and interests. Most Internet Browsers allow you to erase, block or give you a warning before a Cookie is stored. You will be able to visit most of the areas on our websites without a cookie being stored. 

##  Links to other sites

We do occasionally provide links to 3rd party websites on our websites. We add these links to provide further information and enjoyment of your web experience from our websites. We try to thoroughly review the websites we link to, however, we are not responsible for the content or information collection practices of those pages. Please read the privacy of any website you visit before providing them with personal information. 

##  age restrictions

We love having your children visit our websites with you, and hope our websites are fun and educational for your children. However, child privacy law states you cannot provide us with personal information if you are under the age of 13. If you do provide us with personal information, you represent that you are at least 13 years old. We ask that parents register any Panda Cards purchased for their children in the name of the parent of guardian. 

##  Changes

We may at some point make changes to this privacy policy. We will only use information as specified under whatever privacy policy was posted at the time of collection. If we would like to use information differently, we will send an e-mail asking your permission and only use the information if you give us consent. 

##  contact us

If you wish to change or delete your registration information or opt-out of any promotional materials please contact us at "Contact Us" at www.pandaexpress.com. To update your information concerning your Panda Card please contact us at www.mypandacard.com. 

##  Panda express gift card agreement

Read terms and conditions that apply to the prepaid account of your card.
